we should buy a bar barbar would be
awesome and dude dude dude yes no idea
my your hi I'm sorry Lilly has no idea
am i okay I'm gonna try and tell this
story without completely losing it I was
at there nope not gonna happen give me a
second I was at the bar I had thought of
everything except wait just professor
everyone effort to faster just do
something I think that's right what do
you expect to meet some cute travel
agent when you're reading a newspaper at
a bookstore none of those things exist
anymore
fine it's fire for my Play Oh Lilly I'd
love to but we're not in college and I'm
not trying to sleep with you
I appreciate it up but there's a reason
your name is Robin not Batman hell I'd
never put up with that I only had sex
with one girl your whole life Barney I'm
pregnant
hey Barney
see that girl oh yeah you just know she
likes it dirty so my husband sent off to
go parasailing and he wants me to join
you yes oh that's weird I just left Phil
reception yes
weird I can't go I've got this thing
penis do you know what I saw on my way
in here a girl in a sweater Hong Kong he
moved there for business had the only
reason to wait a month for sex as if the
girl is 17 years 11 months old
you can grab life by the crack and lick
the crap out of a licker yeah call her
I'm sorry can you repeat that
I don't speak I never get laid our mail
carrier hates me ever since I asked her
when the baby was due no he was
old-fashioned but I need to have sex
with a girl at least three times before
I'll even consider having dinner with
her what's his name guy in I'm sorry
Gail Kyle
girl enjoy yourselves have fun but don't
touch anything
thank you challenge accepted a real man
chooses his own name
I'm galactic president superstar
mcawesomeville College it's a confusing
time desperately need these are 18
Ewing's Ted these are 18 year olds May
one way I'm better than that guy you're
bigger I win